我叫麦克斯
My name is Max.
我的世界充斥着火与血
My world is fire and blood.
你为什么伤害这些人
Why are you hurting these people?
- 石油 蠢货 - 石油之战
- It's the oil, stupid. - Oil wars.
- 我们为汽油杀人 - 汽油
- We are killing for guzzoline. - Guzzoline.
世界上的水资源已经枯竭
The world is actually running out of water.
水资源之战 水资源之战
Now there's the water wars, water wars.
我曾经是一名警察
Once, I was a cop,
一位追寻正义的公路战士
A road warrior searching for a righteous cause.
无可救药的疯狂
To the terminal freak-out point.
人类已经失控 毛骨悚然
Mankind has gone rogue, terrorizing itself.
热核之战
Thermonuclear skirmish.
地球是酸臭的
The earth is sour.
剧毒深入骨髓
Our bones are poisoned.
我们只剩半条命
We have become half-life.
世界陨落之时
As the world fell...
每个人都支离破碎
each of us in our own way was broken.
很难分辨谁更疯狂
It was hard to know who was more crazy.
是我 还是其他人
me or everyone else.
你好
Hello?
你在哪
Where are you?
你在哪 麦克斯
Where are you Max?
- 他们又来了 - 麦克斯·洛克坦斯基
- Here they come again. - Max rockatansky.
蠕动着侵入我大脑内的黑暗深渊
Worming their way into the black matter of my brain.
救救我们 麦克斯
Help us Max!
你保证会救我们的
You promised to help us!
我告诉自己
I tell myself...
他们无法伤害我
they cannot touch me.
他们早就死了
They are long dead.
跟着他
After him!
动手
Now!
我逃离活人 也逃离亡魂
I am the one who runs from both the living and the dead,
被秃鹫捕猎
Hunted by scavengers...
被我辜负的冤魂纠缠
Haunted by those I could not protect.
我在这片废墟里挣扎…
So I exist in this wasteland...
人性中只剩下一个本能
A man, reduced to a single instinct:
活下去
Survive.
(O型阴性 高质量血液 通用血主)
麦克斯 ？麦克斯 ？
Max? Max?
是你吗
Is that you?
你去哪了
Where were you?
- 救救我们 - 你去哪了
- Help us. - Where were you?
救救我们 麦克斯
Help us, Max.
- 你去哪了 麦克斯 - 救救我们
- Where were you, Max? - Help us!
救救我们 麦克斯
Help us, Max.
别跑了
Stop running.
- 你害死了我们 - 你害死了我们
- You let us die. - You let us die.
你害死了我们
You let us die!
你保证会救我们的
You promised to help us.
为什么
Why?
见证我
Witness!
《疯狂的麦克斯4：狂暴之路》
我们是战争男孩
We are war boys!
战争男孩
War boys!
勇猛战争男孩
Kamakrazee war boys!
战争男孩
War boys!
狂暴勇猛战争男孩
Fucacima kamakrazee war boys!
钩上去
Hooked on!
今天我们要去汽油镇
Today we're headin' to gas town!
汽油镇
Gas town!
我们要拖走可乐水
Today we're haulin' aqua cola.
可乐水
Aqua cola!
我们要拖走农作物
Today we're haulin' produce!
农作物
Produce!
我们还要拖走乳汁
And today we're haulin' mother's milk!
乳汁
Mother's milk!
乔 乔 乔 不死老乔
Joe! Joe! Joe! Immortan Joe!
欢呼不死老乔
Rev it up for the immortan Joe!
我再次派出战车
Once again, we send off my war rig
从汽油镇带回汽油
to bring back guzzoline from gas town
从子弹农场带回子弹
and bullets from the bullet farm.
我再次向我的猛将弗里莎致敬
Once again, I salute my imperator, furiosa!
我向半条命战争男孩致敬
And I salute my half-life war boys
他们将随我一起
who will ride with me eternal
前往永生的英灵殿
on the highways of Valhalla.
冲锋 冲锋 冲锋 冲锋
Assault! Assault! Assault!
我是你们的救世主
I am your redeemer!
追随我 你们将从这片尘土中崛起
It is by my hand you will rise from the ashes of this world!
要来了 快准备
It's comin'. G-get ready.
太好了 要来了
Yes. Yes. Yes. It's comin'.
臣民们 不要沉迷于水
Do not, my friends, become addicted to water.
它会控制你们
It will take hold of you.
让你们憎恶它的缺失
And you will resent its absence.
滚开
Clear off!
把他们弄走
Get 'em all off!
快滚开
Clear off!
给汽油镇发讯号 车队出发了
Signal gas town. Convoy's on its way.
有一个战争男孩快没血了
I got a war boy runnin' on empty.
把那个满血的吊起来
Hook up that full-life.
嘿 小心点 那可是个万能输血者
Hey! Careful. That's a universal donor.
老大 我们不去汽油镇吗
Boss, we're not going to Gas Town?
子弹农场
Bullet Farm?
我们向东走
We're heading east!
我把话传下去
I'll pass it down the line.
新命令
New orders!
打起精神来 打起精神来
Thunder up! Thunder up!
我们不去补充供给了
This is not a supply run!!
- 走 走 - 王牌 怎么回事
- Go. Go. Go. - Ace, what's going on?
- 我们向东走 - 为什么
- We're heading east. - Why?
我不知道 这是命令
I don't know. That's the order.
好
Moo.
- 嘿 老爹 - 嗯
- Hey, pa. - Hm?
你知道吗
You know about this?
你的车队没去汽油镇
Your produce ain't going to gas town.
她偏离了路线
She's gone off-road...
去敌方地盘上了
Into hostile territory.
她为什么要这么做 老爹
Why would she do that, dad?
让我看看 让我看看
Let me see. Let me see.
- 裂齿 - 我想看
- Rictus. - I wanna see!
咧嘴 去看看老爹为什么生气
Rictus, go see what's agitating dad!
绚丽
Splendid!
安哈拉德
Angharad!
(我们的孩子绝不做军阀)
(谁杀死了世界)
她们在哪
Where are they?
她们不是你的所有物
They are not your property.
吉迪小姐
Miss giddy?
你无法拥有一个人类
You cannot own a human being.
总有一天有人会反抗
Sooner or later someone pushes back!
她要把她们带去哪里
Where is she taking them?!
她没带她们走 是她们求她的
She didn't take them. They begged her to go!
她要把她们带去哪
Where is she taking them?
远离你
A long way from you!
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's happening?
撕裂
Slit.
发生了什么 撕裂
What's going on? Slit!
叛国 背叛 一个主将叛逃了
Treason, betrayal, an imperator gone rogue.
一个主将 谁
An imperator. Who?
弗里莎
Furiosa.
她从不死老乔那带走了很多东西
She took a lot of stuff from immortan Joe.
什么东西
W-what stuff?
孕育者
Breeders.
他最优质的孕育者
His prize breeders.
他要她们毫发无损地回来
He wants them back. Not a hand laid on 'em.
以我之功绩敬仰他 八缸战车
By my deeds, I honor him. V-8.
这是我的方向盘
That's my wheel.
我来驾驶
I'm driving.
你是我的枪骑兵
You're my lancer.
我刚给自己升了职
I just promoted myself.
今天不行 今天是属于我的
Not today. Today is my day.
看看你自己
Look at you!
你站都站不起来 根本上不了战场
If you can't stand up, you can't do war!
他说得对 孩子
He's right, son.
我不要待在这里 碌碌无为地死去
I'm not staying here dying a sloth!
你已经是一具尸体了
You're already a corpse.
- 我只是需要一点补给 - 没时间了
- I just need a little top-up. - There's no time!
我们带上我的血袋
We take my Blood Bag.
我们带上我的血袋 把他绑在枪骑兵杆上
We take my blood bag and strap him to the lancer's perch.
它戴着口套 是个疯狂的逃兽
It's got a muzzle on it. It's a raging feral!
这就对了
That's right!
让我充满疯狂的高辛烷值血液
High-octane crazy blood filling me up.
如果我要死…
If I'm gonna die...
我也要光荣地死在狂暴之路上
I'm gonna die historic on the Fury Road!
没错 没错
Yeah. Yeah.
阿机
Organic.
嗯
Yeah?
装上他的血袋
Hitch up his blood bag.
没问题
Right-o.
太棒了
Yeah!
他们到底还想夺走我多少东西
Ah! How much more can they take from me?
他们已经抽了我的血 现在又是我的车
They've got my blood. Now it's my car!
不死神
Immortan!
不死老乔
Immortan Joe!
他看我了
He looked at me!
He looked right at me!
他看的是你的血袋
He looked at your blood bag!
他转头了
He turned his head.
他看了我的眼睛
He looked me straight in the eye.
他只是在环视周围
He was scanning the horizon.
不
No.
我被选中了
I am awaited.
我会进入英灵殿
I am awaited in Valhalla!
(纳克斯)
操
Confucamus!
不死神
Immortan!
耶
Yeah!
嘿 注意
Hey! Heads up!
注意
Heads up!
老大
Boss!
末日堡垒派来了车
We got vehicles from the citadel.
他们在发射信号弹
They're firing flares.
他们在向汽油镇和
They want reinforcements
子弹农场请求增援
from gas town and the bullet farm.
怎么回事
What is this?
后援 还是圈套
Backup? Decoy?
我们绕道
It's a detour.
战车在我们的地盘干什么
愚蠢… 自己送上门
看右边
Eyes right.
秃鹫
Buzzards!
右方有秃鹰
Buzzards right!
注意 注意
Eyes on! Eyes on!
右方有秃鹰
Buzzards right!
注意
Eyes on!
注意 耶
Eyes on! Yeah!
我们要掉头 把他们引向后援吗
Should we turn it 'round and run 'em into our backup?
不 我们能行
No. We're good.
我们全速前进
We fang it!
打起精神来 前进
Thunder up! Here we go!
炮手准备
Prepare the gunners!
莫索
Morsov!
快点 攻击
Come on, attack!
战争
War!
准备好了
Ready!
她是我们的 撕裂
She's ours, slit!
她是我们的
She's ours.
我们先处理掉她后面的秃鹫
First, we get the buzzards off her back!
准备攻击
Form up!
当心我的头
That's my head!
站起来 你可以的
Get up! You can do it!
莫索
Morsov!
不
No!
见证我
Witness me!
- 见证 - 见证
- Witness! - Witness!
- 飞啊 - 飞啊
- Fly! - Fly!
- 见证 - 见证
- Witness! - Witness!
中级士兵 莫索
Mediocre, morsov!
中级士兵
Mediocre!
准备
Ready!
准备好
Get ready!
倒车
Back me in!
他们来了
They're coming!
我们在下面没法呼吸
We can't breathe down there!
躲起来
Stay out of sight!
快
Now!
回来
Go back!
液压 液压
Hydraulics! Hydraulics!
耶
Yeah.
现在我们把战利品带回去
Now we bring home the Booty.
她以为她能甩掉我们 老爹
She thinks she can lose us, dad.
她以为我们是蠢货
She thinks we're stupid.
她以为她能在那甩掉我们
She thinks she can lose us in there!
加速
Fang it!
你为什么不停下
Why can't you stop?
平头
Crew!
快让开 快让开
Outta the way! Out of the way!
你做了什么
What have you done?
What have you done?!
我们需要平衡物 把血袋弄到后面
We need counterweight. Get the blood bag down the back.
抓住他们 抓住他们
Hunt them down! Hunt them down!
嘿 脑袋
Hey, head...
和脖子说再见吧
Say bye-bye to the neck!
斩首
Decapito!
我们要进去了 撕裂
We're goin' in, slit!
快点 我们快抓到她了
Come on! We've almost got her!
加把劲 稳住
Come on! Hold it steady!
哦 太棒了
Oh, what a day!
真是太棒了
What a lovely day!
我就是那个…
I am the man...
抓住太阳的人
Who grabs the sun...
驶向英灵殿
riding to Valhalla!
见证我 血袋
Witness me, blood bag!
见证
Witness!
我活着 我死去 我重生
I live, I die, I live again!
我们不会回去
We're not going back.
水
Water.
你
You.
安哈拉德 那只是风
Angharad, is that just the wind,
还是狂暴的折磨
or is it a furious vexation?
我拿到了
I got it!
你给我争光了 血袋 我们活捉了她
Glory me, blood bag! We snagged her alive.
他会撕碎她
He's gonna shred her.
撕碎她
Shred her!
断线钳
Bolt cutters.
锁链
Chain.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey!
看看他们
Oh, look at them.
如此闪耀 如此美丽
So shiny, so chrome.
他会很感激的
He's gonna be so grateful.
我们可以向他要任何东西
We could ask for anything.
我要开战争钻头
I wanna drive the War Rig.
你想要什么
What are you gonna ask for?
这是我的夹克
That's my jacket.
当然
Sure.
你可以要比夹克更好的东西
I mean, you can ask for more than a jacket.
我们要去绿洲
We're going to the green place.
等等 你和我都可以
Wait, it's you and me.
我们要去众母之地的绿洲
We're going to the green place of many mothers.
感觉如何
How does it feel?
很疼
It hurts.
在外面 一切都令人疼痛
Out here, everything hurts.
你们想摆脱困境吗
You wanna get through this?
照我说的做
Do as I say.
现在捡起手边的东西 然后跑
Now pick up what you can and run.
激发开关
Kill switches.
我亲手设置了序列
I set the sequence myself.
除了我没人能开走这辆车
This rig goes nowhere without me.
你可以上车
You can get in.
她们也要一起
Not without them.
那我们就等着
So we wait.
你指望一个十恶不赦的人会感激你吗
You're relying on the gratitude of a very bad man.
你已经伤害了他的一个妻子
You've already damaged one of his wives.
你觉得他能有多感激你
How grateful do you think he's gonna be?
你坐在一个两千马力
You're sitting on 2,000 horsepower
氮驱动的战争机器里
of nitro-boosted war machine.
你大约有五分钟的时间优势
I'd say you've got about a five-minute head start.
你想从脸上取下那玩意吗
You want that thing off your face?
上车
Let's go.
那么多条腿可以让你打
Of all the legs you had to shoot,
你偏偏打中了他最爱的那条
that one was attached to his favorite.
臭屌
Smeg!
你不用非得按他说的做
You don't have to do it just because he tells you.
她有其他选择吗
What choice does she have?
他不会伤害我们的 他需要我们
He's not gonna hurt us. He needs us.
- 为什么 - 讨价还价
- Why? - To bargain.
他还是会伤害我们的
Oh, he'll hurt us, all right.
- 你觉得他会去绿洲吗 - 绝不可能
- Do you think he's coming to the green place? - Never!
他是个喜欢吸屌的疯子
He's a crazy smeg who eats schlanger!
快让开
Ah, stay out of there.
你后面
Behind you.
汽油镇的人
The gas town boys.
别伤害你的筹码
Don't damage the goods.
你看见了什么
What do you see?
大型战车
Big rigs.
臭鼬
Polecats.
火焰枪手
Flamers.
还有食人者
And there's the people eater himself.
是来权衡得失的
Coming to count the cost.
后面有东西在拖我们
We're dragging something out back.
我觉得是油罐
I think it's the fuel pod.
不 不
No, no.
我去
I'll go.
贱人 你背叛了他
Filth! You traited him!
不要滥杀无辜
No unnecessary killing!
这个战争男孩想杀了我
This war boy wants me dead!
我们说好的
We agreed!
他彻底疯了
He's kamakrazee!
他只是个将死的半条命男孩
He's just a kid at the end of his half-life.
不 我活着 我死去 我重生
No! I live, I die, I live again!
- 摁住他 - 捆起来
- Hold him! - Tie him up!
把他扔出去
Throw him out!
扔出去
Chuck him out.
你又有伙伴了
You got more friends.
子弹农夫
Bullet farmer.
- 他们从子弹农场来 - 是吗
- They're coming from the bullet farm. - Yeah?
结束了 你无法反抗他
It's over. You can't defy him.
走着瞧 小兄弟
Just watch us, mate.
他是那个抓住太阳的人
He is the one who grabbed the sun.
他把你骗得团团转 战争男孩
Look at how slick he's fooled you, war boy!
他是个老骗子
He's a lying old man.
他会带领我们崛起
By his hand, we'll be lifted up!
所以我们背上才会被烙下他的标记
That's why we have his logo seared on our backs!
生育母畜 战斗炮灰
"Breeding stock!" "Battle fodder!"
不 我被选中了
No, I am awaited!
你只是那个老头的炮灰
You're an old man's battle fodder!
杀死所有人 毁掉一切
Killing everyone and everything!
这不是我们的错
We're not to blame!
那么谁杀死了世界
Then who killed the world?
我之前做了个交易 让我们安全通过
I made a deal up ahead. Safe passage.
不知道现在是否还算数
I don't know if it's still any good.
回到舱底去
Get back in the hold!
别关顶盖
Keep the hatch open.
我需要你留在这里
I need you here.
你也许需要开车
You may have to drive the rig.
你
You.
你留下
You stay.
你待在那里
You stay there.
无论怎样 你不能被人看见
Whatever you do, you can't be seen.
我应该一个人来 这是交易条件
I'm supposed to be alone. That was the deal.
下来
Down here.
嘿
Hey.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
我该怎么叫你
What do I call you?
这重要吗
Does it matter?
好吧
Fine.
我大喊:"蠢货"
When I yell "fool,"
你立刻开车迅速离开
you drive out of here as fast as you can.
这是密码序列 一
This is the sequence... one.
一 二
One, two.
一
One.
红色 黑色 启动
Red, black, go.
记住了吗
You have it?
都在这里
It's all here!
三千加仑的汽油
Three thousand gallons of guzzoline,
照你们的要求
just like you asked!
我把油罐卸下来
I'm gonna unhitch the pod.
你们就投下岩石
You drop the rocks.
你说 "只有几辆车在追你
You said, "a few vehicles in pursuit.
大概"
Maybe."
现在有三支军队在你后面
We count three war parties!
好吧 我运气不好
Yeah, well, I got unlucky.
咱们开始吧
Let's do this!
蠢货
Fool!
那是我们的汽油
That's our fuel!
给锯齿车让路
Make way for the Ripsaw!
我过去之后 清理石头
Once I'm over, clear the rocks
让所有人过去
and bring everyone through.
不死神 不死老乔
Immortan! Immortan Joe!
这个战争男孩说他曾上过战车
I got a war boy! Says he was on the war rig!
你 上车
You! Climb aboard!
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
我找到了他的靴子
I got his boot!
我找到了血袋的靴子
I got the blood bag's boot!
带上我
Take me!
我找到了他的靴子
I got his boot!
这一切都是因为家庭纠纷
All this for a family squabble.
健康的孩子
Healthy babies.
装满弹匣
Reload the clip.
我不会
I-I can't.
枪
Gun!
- 给我枪 - 还没装好
- Give me the gun! - It's not loaded yet!
- 你 - 快点
- You! - Now!
我们有约在先
We had a deal!
裂齿
Rictus!
那些妻子
The wives!
别喷火了
No more flames.
绚丽
Splendid!
那是我的孩子
That's my child!
我的所有物
My property!
不死…
Immorta...
不死神 如果我能上战车 我知道怎么进去
Immortan, if I get on the rig, there's a way inside.
- 你叫什么 - 我叫纳克斯
- What is your name? - I It's Nux.
我会刺中她的脊椎 把她的命留给你
I'll pike her in the spine. Keep her breathing for ya.
不
No.
一枪打穿她的脑袋 停下战车
Put a bullet in her skull, stop the rig,
把我的孕育者带回来
return my treasures to me,
我会亲自带你
and I myself will carry you
前往英灵殿之门
to the gates of Valhalla.
我被选中了吗
Am I awaited?
你会永垂不朽 闪耀而美丽
You will ride eternal... shiny and chrome.
裂齿
Rictus!
帮他上车
Help him aboard!
准备好了吗
Ready?
去吧
Here we go!
庸才
Mediocre!
臭屌
Schlanger!
当心
Look out!
安哈拉德
Angharad!
快下车
Get out!
不 安哈拉德
No! Angharad!
停下 快掉头
Stop! Turn the rig around!
回去救她
Go back for her!
不
No.
和他说 让他掉头
Tell him to turn the rig around!
你看见了吗
Did you see it?
她被轮子碾过去了
She went under the wheels.
你看见了吗
Did you see it?
她被车轮碾过去了
She went under the wheels.
我们继续前进
We keep moving.
- 不 - 我们继续前进
- No! - We keep moving!
他不知道自己在说什么
He doesn't know what he's talking about!
不管发生什么 我们都要去绿洲
Whatever happens, we're going to the green place.
那该死的绿洲
The stupid green place.
我们甚至不知道它在哪里
We don't even know where to find it.
你没事吧
You all right?
继续追
On! On!
绮朵
Cheedo!
绮朵 别犯傻
Cheedo, don't be stupid.
- 停下 - 他会原谅我们的 一定会的
- Stop! - He'll forgive us. I know he will.
没有回头路
There is no going back!
我们是他的珍宝
We were his treasures!
- 绮朵 - 我们被他呵护
- Cheedo! - We were protected.
他给我们最好的待遇
He gave us the high life.
- 那有什么错 - 我们不是物品
- What wrong with that? - We are not things.
不
No!
绮朵 我们不是物品
Cheedo, we are not things!
我们不是物品
We are not things.
我不想再听到这句话
I don't want to hear that again!
这是她说的
They were her words!
现在她死了
And now she's dead!
无论你如何痛苦挣扎
Wring your hands and tear your hair,
你都不能回到他身边
You're not going back to him.
安哈拉德
Angharad!
起来 起来
Come on! Come on!
所以 呃…
So, um...
这个…
Where is this...
绿洲在哪里
This green place?
向东行驶一整晚
It's a long night's run, heading east.
我们需要子弹清单
We need inventory.
我要你把每把枪的子弹对上号
I want you to match every gun with its bullets.
我下去做些修理
I'm gonna go down and do some repairs.
后面需要一个人放哨
We need someone down the back.
- 我去 - 不行
- I'll go. - No.
你们待在一起
I want you to stay together.
我可以的
I can do it.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
他看见了
He saw it.
他什么都看见了
He saw it all.
我的血袋开着战车杀死了她
My own blood bag drivin' the rig that killed her.
快停下
Stop doing that.
嘘 嘘 嘘
Shh, shh, shh.
停下
Stop.
大门曾向我敞开了三次
Thr... three times the gates were open to me.
什么大门
What gates?
我被英灵殿召唤了
I was awaited in Valhalla.
他们在呼唤我的名字
They were calling my name.
我本可以随不死神一起
I should be walking with the immorta,
与诸代先烈畅怀豪饮
mcfeasting with the heroes of all time.
也许你的命运并非如此
I'd say it was your manifest Destiny not to.
我以为我终于得到了一些美好的东西
I thought I was being spared for something great.
我开上了追捕车
I got to drive a pursuit vehicle.
有一阵子 甚至拉瑞和巴瑞都不再折磨我
For a while even Larry and Barry stopped chewing on my windpipe.
谁是拉瑞和巴瑞
Who are Larry and Barry?
我的伙伴
My mates.
拉瑞和巴瑞
Larry and Barry.
就算它们没杀死我 夜热也会要了我的命
If they don't get me, then the night fevers will.
这把大家伙只剩四颗子弹了
Well, we've only got four for big boy here,
所以它基本报废了
so he's all but useless.
但我们还能用这把小家伙
But we can squirt off this little pinky
射二十九次
a raunchy 29 times.
安哈拉德以前管它叫叛逆之种
Angharad used to call them Anti-seed.
种下一颗 收获死亡
Plant one and watch something die.
我们损失了三万升汽油
We are down 30,000 units of guzzoline,
十九罐氮气 十二辆攻击型摩托
19 canisters of nitro, 12 assault bikes,
七辆追捕车
7 pursuit vehicles.
亏损严重
The deficit mounts.
现在 阁下 你又害我们陷进了泥潭
And now, sir, you have us stuck in a quagmire.
嘿 老乔
Hey, Joe!
老大
Boss!
你的女人快不行了
Your girly's breathing her last!
那孩子呢
What about the child?
你来不来 兄弟
Are ya comin', brother?
等等
Wait!
里面什么动静都没有
It's gone awful quiet in there.
取出来
Get it out.
把他取出来
Get it out!
快点 我等不及要去折磨叛徒了
Come on! I've been called to the torture!
耐心点
Patience!
你就待在这里伤心吧 老爹
Oh, you stay here with your grief, daddy.
我去帮你抓他们
I'll fetch 'em for ya.
小心点 别损坏我的财产
Be careful! Protect the assets!
只需要一颗子弹
Just one angry shot...
杀死弗里莎
For furiosa.
出发
Hut!
真可惜
Cryin' shame.
再过一个月
Another month...
也许就是个健康的孩子
Could've been your viable human.
是男孩吗
Was it a male?
是个小男子汉
Your a-one Alpha prime.
嘿 裂齿
Hey, rictus!
你失去了一个小弟弟
You lost a baby brother.
而且身体健全
Perfect in every way.
我有过一个弟弟
I had a baby brother!
我有过一个小弟弟
I had a little baby brother!
他很完美
And he was perfect!
完美无缺
Perfect in every way!
快点
Come on.
别射到那些女人 老大
Wouldn't wanna shoot the wives, sir.
只是探探路
Just probing.
他想帮忙
He wants to help!
谁
Who?!
那个战争男孩
The war boy!
他从哪冒出来的
Where did he come from?!
我以为我们把他扔下车了
I thought we threw him off the rig!
那个东西后面有一个高地
T-there's high ground just beyond that thing.
他是说那棵树
He means the tree.
对 树
Yeah. Tree!
我来盯着他
Leave him to me.
有人注意到那道亮光了吗
Say, anyone notice that bright light?
有人在向我们开火吗
Encroaching gunfire?
- 出来 - 我可以的 我了解这辆车
- Get out. - I-I can do this. I know this machine.
的确 他是驾驶员
He does. He's a revhead.
你还剩两发子弹
You've got two left.
盯着他
On him.
屏住呼吸
Don't breathe.
嘿
Hey!
嘿 嘿 战争男孩
Hey! Hey! War boy!
我去把铰链缠在那个树上面
I'm gonna use the winch 'round the tree thing!
拿着枪 我们去拿引擎板
Take this. Let's get the engine plates.
你去开车
You drive the rig!
- 举起火炬 - 我正举着火炬
- Hold up a flare. - I am holding a flare!
再近点
Closer.
就在你眼前
It's right in front of your eyes!
出发 出发
Hut! Hut!!
血袋
Blood bag!
我是正义的使者
I am the scales of justice!
死亡的掌控者
Conductor of the choir of death!
惨叫吧 叛徒们
Sing, brother Koch!
惨叫吧 叛徒 惨叫吧
Sing, brothers, sing!
惨叫吧
Sing!
难道他们不知道会打到我们吗
Don't they know they're shooting at us?
枪林热弹
Gun fever!
我从没想过自己能做如此厉害的事
I never thought I'd do something as shine as that.
引擎怎么样
How are the engines?
过烫 而且需要加油
Very hot and real thirsty.
嘿
Hey.
你把战车沿着路向下开半公里
You need to take the war rig half a click down the track.
要是引擎冷却之后
What if you're not back
你还没回来怎么办
by the time the engines have cooled?
你们继续前进
Well, you keep moving.
你觉得他想做什么
What do you suppose he's gonna do?
以血还血
Retaliate first.
我们走
Let's go!
你受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
嗯
Huh?
你在流血
You're bleeding.
那不是他的血
That's not his blood.
这是什么
What is this?
这是乳汁
It's mother's milk.
没事的
It's okay.
睡吧
Sleep.
好好休息
Get some rest.
你怎么知道那地方真的存在
How do you know this place even exists?
我出生在那里
I was born there.
那你为什么离开
So why'd you leave?
我没有
I didn't.
我小时候被带走了
I was taken as a child.
被偷走了
Stolen.
你以前做过这种事吗
You done this before?
很多次
Many times.
现在我开战车
Now that I drive a war rig...
这是我最好的机会
This is the best shot I'll ever have.
那她们呢
And them?
她们在寻找希望
They're looking for hope.
那你呢
What about you?
救赎
Redemption.
嘿 那是什么
Hey, what's that?
我曾见过那样的东西
I remember something like that.
救救我
Help me!
Help me, please!
那是诱饵
That's bait.
待在车里
Stay in the rig.
快点 求求你 他们快回来了
Hurry! Please, hurry! They'll be back!
我是乌乌里尼的族人
I'm one of the Vuvalini!
众母之女
Of the Many Mothers!
我的启蒙母亲是凯蒂·肯嘉尼
My initiate mother was Katie Concannon!
我是玛丽·杰巴萨的女儿
I am the daughter of Mary Jabassa.
我是幼犬家族的人
My clan was swaddle dog!
是我
It's me.
她的这种眼神
There's something in the eyes.
也许她真的是杰巴萨的孩子
Perhaps it is Jabassa's child.
这是我们的弗里莎
This is our furiosa.
有多久了
How long has it been?
七千天
7,000 days.
还有那些我尚未记事的日子
Plus the ones I don't remember.
弗里莎
Furiosa.
你母亲怎么了
What happened to your mother?
她死了
She died.
在我出生后的第三天
On the third day.
你从哪里来
From where did you come?
西边 末日堡垒
The west. Citadel.
在群山后面
Beyond the mountains.
那些男人 他们是谁
The men... who are they?
他们可以信任
They're reliable.
他们帮我们来到这里
They helped us get here.
你从哪找来这些尤物的
Where did you find such creatures?
真柔软
So soft.
这个牙齿长得真好
This one has all her teeth.
我等不及想让他们看
I can't wait for them to see it.
看
See?
看什么
See what?
家园
Home.
绿洲
The green place.
但如果你们从西边来
But if you came from the west,
应该会路过那里
you passed it.
乌鸦
The crows.
令人毛骨悚然的群鸦之地
The creepy place with all the crows.
土壤污染
The soil.
我们只能背井离乡
We had to get out.
- 我们没有水 - 水肮脏无比
- We had no water and... - the water was filth.
- 被污染了 都是酸臭的 - 然后乌鸦来了
- It was poisoned. It was sour. - And the crows came.
我们无法耕种
We couldn't grow anything.
其他人在哪
Where are the others?
什么其他人
What others?
众母
The many mothers.
我们是幸存的
We're the only ones left.
看
Look.
那就是你们口中的卫星
That's what you call a satellite.
吉迪小姐告诉我们的
Miss giddy told us about those.
它们曾用于为地球传送信号
They used to bounce messages across the earth.
电视节目
Shows.
曾经的世界里每个人都有节目
Everyone in the old world had a show.
你觉得现在还有人在那里吗
Do you think there's still somebody out there?
播送节目
Sending shows?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
那是一片寂静荒原
Those are the plains of silence.
乖乖待着别动 小乔
Stay right where you are, little Joe.
外面的世界越发无趣
Kind of lost its novelty out here.
你怀孕了
You having a baby?
军阀的孩子
Warlord Jr.
肯定很丑陋
Gonna be so ugly.
也许是个女孩
It could be a girl.
你用那把抢杀人 对吗
You kill people with that, do ya?
我杀了所有从外面来的人
Killed everyone I ever met out here.
一枪爆头
Headshots, all of 'em.
正中脑髓
Snap. Right in the medulla.
我以为你们早就不这么暴力了
Thought somehow you girls were above all that.
过来
Come here.
来瞧瞧
Take a peek.
种子
Seeds.
这些是家乡的
These are from home.
传家宝 真正的种子
Heirlooms. The real thing.
一有机会 我就种一颗
I plant one every chance I get.
种在哪里
Where?
至今没一株能活 土壤太酸了
So far, nothing's took. Earth's too sour.
种类好多
Ah, so many different kinds.
树 花朵 水果
Trees, flowers, fruit.
当时 每个人都有一份
Back then, everyone had their fill.
当年 我们不必为生存杀人
Back then, there was no need to snap anybody.
我能和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you?
我和其他人谈过了
I've talked with the others.
我们再也不会有更好的机会 穿过这片盐碱地
We're never gonna have a better chance to make it across the salt.
如果我们把战车留在这里
If we leave the rig here
尽量给摩托车加满汽油
and load the motorcycles up with as much as we can,
我们也许能开一百六十天
we can maybe ride for 160 days.
其中一辆摩托是你的
One of those bikes is yours.
加满了油
Fully loaded.
我们很欢迎你加入我们
You're more than welcome to come with us.
我 我走自己的路
I'll... I'll make my own way.
希望是一种错误
You know, hope is a mistake.
如果你无法修补裂纹 你会…
If you can't fix what's broken, you'll, uh...
你会变成疯子
you'll go insane.
你在哪 麦克斯
Where are you, Max?
你在哪
Where are you?
- 救救我 - 救救我们
- Help me. - Help us.
你保证会救我们的
You promised to help us.
快点 爸爸 我们走吧
Come on, pa. Let's go.
好吧
All right.
这是你回家的路
This is your way home.
我们回去
We go back?
- 回去 - 是啊
- Back? - Yeah.
我以为你不再是疯子了
I thought you weren't insane anymore.
他们在说什么
What are they saying?
他想回到他们来的地方
He wants to go back from where they came.
末日堡垒
The citadel.
末日堡垒里有什么
What's there to find at the Citadel?
绿洲
Green.
还有水源
And water.
那里有大量干净的水
There is a ridiculous amounts of clear water.
以及许多粮食
And a lot of crops.
一切应有尽有 只要你不恐高
It's got everything you need, as long as you're not afraid of heights.
水是从哪来的
Where does the water come from?
他从地底深处抽上来的
He pumps it out from deep under the earth.
称之为"可乐水" 并据为己有
Calls it "Aqua Cola", and claims it all for himself.
因为他拥有水 他就拥有我们所有人
And because he owns it, he owns all of us.
我已经讨厌他了
I don't like him already.
翻过群山需要花两周
It'll take two weeks just to scale a wall of mountains.
不
No.
我们原路返回
I suggest we go back the same way we came.
穿过峡谷
Through the canyon.
现在已经畅通无阻了 对吧
It's open. We know that. Right?
他带领军队从那里通过
He brought all his war parties through!
我们开战车向他们冲过去
So we take the war rig and we charge it
冲到他们中间
right through the middle of them.
我们在道口卸下油罐
We can decouple the tanker at the pass.
封住后路
Shut it off behind us.
嘭
Kaboom!
我们要怎样夺取末日堡垒
And how exactly do we take the Citadel?
假设到时候我们还活着
Assuming we're still alive by then?
如果我们能堵住路 那就简单了
If we can block the pass, it'll be easy.
那里只剩下老弱病残
All that's left are his war pups
以及病弱的战争男孩
and war boys too sick to fight.
我们还有纳克斯 他是战争男孩
And we'll be with nux. He's a war boy.
他会带我们回家
He'll be bringing us home,
夺回属于我们的东西 这是他的使命
bringing back what's stolen, as he's meant to.
是啊
Yeah.
听上去像希望
It feels like hope.
我喜欢这个计划
I like this plan.
我们可以重新开始
We can start again.
如同昔日一般
Just like the old days.
听着 这会是艰难的一天
Look, it'll be a hard day.
但我保证 你向那条路骑一百六十天
But I guarantee you that 160 days ridin' that way,
仍是一片荒凉
there's nothin' but salt.
至少那条路 我们也许能够…
At least that way, y'know we might be able to...
共同
Together...
得到某种救赎
Come across some kind of redemption.
战车
War rig!
那是战车
That's the war rig!
是他们
That's them.
他们为什么回来
Why are they going back?
他们想投降吗
Do they wish to surrender?
他们在朝峡谷开去
They are heading for the canyon.
他们想回末日堡垒
They're going back to the citadel!
他们知道那里毫无防备
They know it's undefended!
混帐
Bullocks!
上去 上去
Roll up! Roll up!
快走
Go!
- 你在做什么 - 祈祷
- What are you doing? - I Praying.
- 向谁祈祷 - 任何能聆听的人
- To who? - Anyone that's listening.
开始了 姑娘们
Here we go, girls!
那是我的车
That's mine!
他们想超到前面 刺穿我们的轮胎
He'll try to get in front of us, spike our wheels.
别弄坏引擎
Don't blow my engine.
我去给它加把劲
I'm gonna nudge him.
一点点
Just a little.
你个贱人 你背叛了他
You filth! You traitored him!
回去
Go.
我们得减速了
Got to back off.
一号引擎报废了 二号也快不行了
Engine one is gone. two's about to blow.
好吧
Right.
你是老手吗
Are you a black thumb?
好的 去修一号引擎
All right. Engine one now.
你和我 去五号车轮
You and me, fifth wheel.
我们去解开油罐
We'll unhook the tanker.
一枪解决一个
One man, one bullet.
我看不见了
I cannot see.
- 玛蒂 玛蒂 - 我看不见了
- Maadi! Maadi! - I cannot see.
嘿
Hey!
他们有矛枪和尾犁
Harpoons and plows!
他们在把我们向后拖
They're hauling us back!
留三个螺栓 三个
Leave three bolts. Three.
嘿 你
Hey, you!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
她受伤了
I think she's hurt.
嘿
Hey!
不
No!
嘿
Hey.
留在我身边
Stay with me.
- 留在我身边 - 留在我身边
- Stay with me. - Stay with me.
你还活着吗
Hey Are you there?
你解决那个 我解决她
You finish that! I'll finish her!
英灵殿
Valhalla!
一号引擎恢复了
Engine one's good.
暂时
For now.
她受伤了 她受了很重的伤
She's hurt! She's hurt real bad!
你听见了吗
You hear that?
两辆八缸汽车会被炸飞
We're gonna see two airborne V8s!
我需要你来开车
I'm gonna need you to drive.
我去解决他
I'll get him out of our way.
裂齿 带我走
Rictus! Take me!
绮朵
Cheedo!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
大家伙
Big boy!
上来 上来
Here! Here!
嘿
Hey!
不
No!
记得我吗
Remember me?
他死了
He's dead!
He's dead.
等你安全过去了
When you're across safe,
我就踩紧油门跟上你
I'll jam the throttle and follow you.
快来
Come on!
快点
Hurry!
我们快到峡谷口了
We're nearly at the pass.
见证我
Witness me.
裂齿
Rictus!
她为什么发出那种声音
Why is she making that noise?
她在努力呼吸
She's pumping air into her chest cavity.
她每次呼吸 肺都在衰退
She's collapsing her lungs one breath at a time.
我知道了
I know.
对不起
I am so sorry.
我知道 我知道
I know. I know.
按住这里
Hold it there.
好了
All right.
绑上绷带 压紧
Put that on there. Press it on.
嘿
Hey.
家
Home.
不
N-no.
不 不 不 不
No, no, no. No, no, no, no.
她失血太多
She's exsanguinated.
血都流光了
Drained all her blood.
好
All right!
拿着这些
Hold these.
我们需要这个 谢谢
We need that. Thank you.
针
Needle.
加油
Come on!
拿着
Take this.
让她保持清醒
Keep her awake.
弗里莎
Furiosa.
好了 进去了
Okay, that's not retracting.
好了
There we go.
好了 举着 举着
All right, hold it up. Hold it up.
好了
Okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
进去了 好了
There you go. Okay.
好了
There you go.
麦克斯
Max.
我叫麦克斯
My name is Max.
那是我的名字
That's my name.
从车里出来
Reveal yourself.
他带着什么东西
He's got something.
是不死老乔
It's immortan Joe.
不死老乔死了
The immortan Joe is dead!
弗里莎
Furiosa!
她回来了
She's back.
放他们上去 放他们上去
Let them up! Let them up!
我们开始吧
Let's do it!
让他们上来 快点
Let 'em up. Come on.
(我们该去什么地方 在这片废墟寻找更好的自己 史上第一人)